Finding Aid for Claude Thomas Stoner Photographs and Papers 1870s-1977
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Duplicate Material
  - Duplicate copy negatives (Box 13)
Walton Junction, Mich. -- GRI30
Warren, Ont. -- CPR1
Warsaw, Ind. -- see unclassified photos and negatives under Railroad stations
Waters, Mich. -- LR22
Wellsboro, Ind. PM51
Whitaker, Mich. -- W11
White Cloud, Mich. -- PM101
White River, Mich. -- LR211, LR257
Whitmore Lake, Mich. -- AA115
Windsor, Ont. -- DRT1-6, also unclassified photos and albums under Detroit River Tunnel Co.
Winter --
AA22, AA44, AA119-120, AA152, AA156, AA162-163, AA179, AA225, AA232, AA238
BC6, BC10, DM4, ESE1, GRI3, GRI19, GRI36-40, KC1
LR7, LR13, LR69, LR93, LR141, LR183, LR194, LR213-215, LSMS26
MC21, MC32, MGR9, ML13, MNE7, PM46-47, PM108-109, PM119, PM123-125, X14
Also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad, Grand Rapids & Indiana, and Miscellaneous various railroad topics, and unclassified negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad, Train wrecks, and Miscellaneous various railroad topics
Wolverine, Mich. -- LR171, MC21
Woodville, Mich. -- CWM19, LR134, LR201, LR250
Ypsilanti, Mich. -- AAY4, DJC1, MC10-13, MC39, MC41, NYC34
Yuma, Mich. -- AA135